electronicsinfoline.com 2006-12-10

# ElectronicsInfoline.com | Privacy Policy

| 

### Introduction

We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as "Data" below) that may be collected by us on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. Please take time to read our [Terms of Use](http://www.electronicsinfoline.com/corporate/conditions.php). 

### Collection of Data.

Our registration process requires only a valid e-mail address and a unique user ID and password. Providing us with other information is at your option. The only personally identifiable information collected on this site is submitted to us freely and deliberately by site users. Please take note that your user name, e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on this site. 

### Use of Data.

We may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site. We will make efforts so that your Data will not be provided to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) we find that your use of this site violates our this Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; (vi) or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data in the same manner as we can as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites. 

### Credit Card Information.

We never store any Credit Card Number or associated information, or they are NEVER shared with any third parties. They are also never used for any other transactions. For **_PayPal_** payment, you are directly taken to **_PayPal_** 's SECURE website **before** you enter any Credit Card information. 

### Cookies.

Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to our site. 

### Server logs 

Server logs capture certain non-personally identifying data, such as the time and date of a web visit, the browser and operating system being used, the IP address or domain name of the user's ISP, and the web URL a user linked from. This information is used generally to help us plan system enhancements when necessary and to provide content which is compatible with our visitors' web browsing systems. 

### Children.

We do not allow persons who are ages thirteen or younger to become members of this site. For more information, please contact [our webmaster](http://www.electronicsinfoline.com/rcl/contact_us.php). 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy.

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings. 

### No guarantees.

While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data. 

### Contact Information.

If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free to contact [our webmaster](http://www.electronicsinfoline.com/rcl/contact_us.php).  |
